Office of the Vice-President, Research fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Correspondence, 1968 - 2000; F-86-1; 2.86 m of textual records
  - B. Clayman Vice-President, Research/Dean of Graduate Studies records, 1984 - 2000; F-86-1-3; 18 cm of textual records
    Series consists of records relating to Bruce Clayman's dual appointment as Vice-President, Research and Dean of Graduate Studies. Records include general graduate studies program correspondence and specific correspondence on VISA students, graduate studies budget planning, tuition fees, and departmental review. Records also include Clayman's involvement on the Graduate Issues Committee, the Western Canadian Deans of Graduate Studies, and the Graduate Survey Implementation Task Force.
    Document types include correspondence and working papers, minutes, reports and financial working papers.
    Western Canadian Deans of Graduate Studies Committee; Graduate Survey Implementation Task Force
    - IDRC/SFU Fish Disease Program, 1984 - 1985; F-86-1-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 86-18)
      Creator's original file classification code: R.3.9.4.
    - VISA students, 1992 - 1997; F-86-1-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 86-18)
    - DGS: Research Ethics course, 1994 - 1996; F-86-1-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 86-18)
    - DGS: Budget, 1995; F-86-1-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 86-18)
    - DGS: Tuition Fees, 1995 - 1999; F-86-1-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 86-18)
    - DGS: Graduate Issues Committee, 1995 - 1998; F-86-1-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 86-19)
    - DGS: Dept. Program Review, 1996; F-86-1-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 86-19)
    - DGS: Western Canadian Deans of Graduate Studies, 1996 - 1999; F-86-1-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 86-19)
    - DGS: General, 1998 - 1999; F-86-1-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 86-19)
    - DGS: Graduate Survey Implementation Task Force, 1998 - 1999; F-86-1-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 86-19)
    - DGS: General, 1999 - 2000; F-86-1-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 86-19)
  - Industry correspondence, 1985 - 2000; F-86-1-4; 39 cm of textual records
    Series consists of records relating to correspondence between the Vice-President, Research and companies in the local and international research industry field. For a list of these companies, please see access points below.
    Document types include correspondence and working papers, reports, and publications.
    B.C. Research; SUN Microsystems of Canada; Precarn Associates Inc.; Ventures West; MPR TelTech Ltd.; Scott Paper; BC Tel; Canadian Microelectronic Corp.; IBM; General Electric Canada; NCompass; Lohn Foundation; TransTech; Knowledge Network; Nortel; Electronic Arts
    - B.C. Research, 1985 - 1992; F-86-1-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 86-19)
    - SUN Microsystems of Canada, 1988 - 1989; F-86-1-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 86-20)
    - Triathalon, vol. 1, 1988 - 1991; F-86-1-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 86-20)
    - Triathalon, vol. 2, 1988 - 1991; F-86-1-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 86-20)
    - Precarn Associates Inc., vol. 1, 1988 - 1994; F-86-1-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 86-20)
    - Precarn Associates Inc., vol. 2, 1988 - 1994; F-86-1-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 86-20)
    - Discovery Foundation - Trustees general, 1989 - 1992; F-86-1-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 86-20)
    - Ventures West, 1992; F-86-1-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 86-21)
    - Elemental Research, 1993 - 1994; F-86-1-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 86-21)
    - MPR TelTech Ltd., 1993 - 1995; F-86-1-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 86-21)
    - Pacific Glass Management: Bottle Smart, 1993 - 1995; F-86-1-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 86-21)
    - MEL/IMMR Cooperation Agreement, 1994; F-86-1-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 86-21)
    - Scott Paper, 1994 - 1995; F-86-1-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 86-21)
    - Newbridge ATM Research Partnership, 1994 - 1996; F-86-1-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 86-21)
    - BC Tel, 1994 - 1996; F-86-1-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 86-21)
    - Canadian Microelectronic Corp., 1994 - 1996; F-86-1-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 86-21)
    - IBM, 1995 - 1996; F-86-1-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 86-21)
    - GE Canada, 1995 - 1996; F-86-1-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 86-21)
    - MPR TelTech Ltd., 1996; F-86-1-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 86-22)
    - MPR TelTech Ltd. Cleanrooms, 1996; F-86-1-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 86-22)
    - NCompass, 1996 - 1997; F-86-1-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 86-22)
    - Lohn Foundation, 1996 - 1997; F-86-1-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 86-22)
      Open
    - TransTech, 1996 - 1997; F-86-1-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 86-22)
    - IBM, 1996 - 1999; F-86-1-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 86-22)
    - Knowledge Network, 1997 - 1999; F-86-1-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 86-22)
    - Nortel, 1997 - 2000; F-86-1-4-0-26 (Archival box - standard 86-22)
    - IRIS Precarn, 1998 - 1999; F-86-1-4-0-27 (Archival box - standard 86-22)
    - Electronic Arts, 1998 - 1999; F-86-1-4-0-28 (Archival box - standard 86-22)
    - BC Tel, 1998 - 1999; F-86-1-4-0-29 (Archival box - standard 86-22)
    - Canadian Light Source, 1999; F-86-1-4-0-30 (Archival box - standard 86-22)
  - Government correspondence, 1984 - 1996; F-86-1-5; 9 cm of textual records
    Series consists of records relating to correspondence between the Vice-President, Research and government agencies regarding support and promotion of research. For a list of these agencies, please see access points below.
    Document types include correspondence, working papers, and reports.
    National Research Council; Ministry of Advanced Education; Industry Canada; Ministry of Employment and Investment
    - National Research Council: SFU location, 1984 - 1986; F-86-1-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 86-22)
    - Provincial Government, 1989 - 1990; F-86-1-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 86-23)
    - Ministry of Advanced Education - S.T.D.F., 1990 - 1991; F-86-1-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 86-23)
    - Government - general correspondence, 1993 - 1996; F-86-1-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 86-23)
    - Industry Canada, 1994 - 1996; F-86-1-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 86-23)
    - Federal Science and Technology Review, 1994 - 1996; F-86-1-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 86-23)
    - Ministry of Employment and Investment, 1994 - 1996; F-86-1-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 86-23)
- Financial records, 1979 - 1998; F-86-2; 19 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records of the Vice-President, Research relating to budget development, research fellowships and grants including the W.A.C. Bennett Fund, the Macmillan Family Fund, and the R.H. Wright Olfactory Prize. Records also include correspondence with the Natural Science and Engineering Research Council (NSERC), the National Research Council, Social Sciences and Humanities Research Council (SSHRC).
  Document types include correspondence, working papers, financial statistics, and reports.
  Natural Science and Engineering Research Council; Social Sciences and Humanities Research Council; National Research Council
  - Budget records, 1993 - 1996; F-86-2-1; 4 cm of textual records
    - Budgets - SFU 94/95, 1993 - 1995; F-86-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 86-23)
    - Library budget, 1993 - 1996; F-86-2-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 86-23)
    - Budgets - SFU 96/97, 1994 - 1996; F-86-2-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 86-23)
  - Grant records, 1979 - 1998; F-86-2-2; 14 cm of textual records
    - W.A.C. Bennett Fund, 1979 - 1984; F-86-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 86-24)
    - NSERC Research Fellowships Applications, vol. 1, 1983 - 1984; F-86-2-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 86-24)
    - NSERC Research Fellowships Applications, vol. 2, 1983 - 1984; F-86-2-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 86-24)
    - Macmillan Family Fund, 1984; F-86-2-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 86-24)
    - R.H. Wright Olfactory Prize, 1984 - 1985; F-86-2-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 86-24)
    - Matching funds, 1986 - 1991; F-86-2-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 86-24)
    - National Research Council, 1988 - 1996; F-86-2-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 86-24)
    - Tricouncil grant, 1992 - 1993; F-86-2-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 86-24)
    - SSHRC: Summer Institute, 1994 - 1995; F-86-2-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 86-24)
    - NSERC: general correspondence, vol. 1, 1994 - 1996; F-86-2-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 86-24)
    - NSERC: general correspondence, vol. 2, 1994 - 1996; F-86-2-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 86-24)
    - SSHRC general research grants, vol. 1, 1995 - 1998; F-86-2-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 86-25)
    - SSHRC general research grants, vol. 2, 1995 - 1998; F-86-2-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 86-25)
- Centres and Institutes, 1979 - 1998; F-86-3; 85 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to research centres and institutes formed by SFU researchers, or operated under partnership with SFU, that reported to the Vice-President, Research. Some of the centres and institutes have been disbanded due to inactivity. For a list of all centres and institutes, see the list of access points below.
  Document types include correspondence, working papers, budgets, policies and procedures, and reports.
  Theoretical Science Institute; Criminology Research Centre; Geraldine and Tong Louie Research Centre for Rehabilitation, Ergonomics and Human Performance; Historical Records Institute; Chemical Ecology Research Group; Instructional Psychology Research Group; Institute for Criminal Justice Policy; Energy Research Institute; Institute for International Development; Laboratory for Computer and Communications Research; Psychology and Law Institute; Computing Science Instructional Lab; Institute for Studies of Criminal Justice Policy; Institute for Quaternary Research; Institute for Applied Logic; Incubation Centre; Wireless Communications Research Centre; BCIT Development Assist Centre; Back Testing Unit Centre; Centre for Image and Sound Research; Enterprise Development Centre; Integrated Media Centre; Business Development Centre; Advanced Systems Institute; Networks of Centres of Excellence; Sustainable Development Research Institute; C.D. Howe Institute; Medical Devices Development Centre; Canada ASEAN Centre; Institute for Sensor and Control Tech Steering Committee
  - Theoretical Science Institute, 1979 - 1981; F-86-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 86-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: 16.1.
  - Criminology Research Centre, 1979 - 1982; F-86-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 86-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.4.6.14.90.
  - Institute for Human Performance, 1979 - 1982; F-86-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 86-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.4.10.15.30.
  - Historical Records Institute, 1979 - 1992; F-86-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 86-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.4.9.15.20.
  - Chemical Ecology Research Group, 1980 - 1982; F-86-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 86-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.4.5.14.80.
  - Instructional Psychology Research Group, 1980 - 1982; F-86-3-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 86-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.4.15.15.80.
  - Institute for Criminal Justice Policy, 1980 - 1982; F-86-3-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 86-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.4.1.15.40.
  - Energy Research Institute, vol. 1, 1980 - 1994; F-86-3-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 86-25)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.4.7.15.00.
  - Energy Research Institute, vol. 2, 1980 - 1994; F-86-3-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 86-25)
  - Institute for International Development, 1981 - 1982; F-86-3-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 86-26)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.4.13.15.60.
  - Laboratory for Computer and Communications Research, 1982; F-86-3-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 86-26)
    Creator's original file classification code: 3.4.16.15.90.
  - Psychology and Law Institute, vol. 1, 1982 - 1992; F-86-3-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 86-26)
  - Psychology and Law Institute, vol. 2, 1982 - 1992; F-86-3-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 86-26)
  - Psychology and Law Institute, vol. 3, 1982 - 1992; F-86-3-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 86-26)
  - Computing Science Instructional Lab (CSIL), 1983 - 1984; F-86-3-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 86-26)
    Creator's original file classification code: R.1.2.8.
  - Institute for Studies of Criminal Justice Policy, 1983 - 1984; F-86-3-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 86-26)
    Creator's original file classification code: R.1.2.2.
  - Remote Sensing Facility in the SFU Institute for Quaternary Research, 1984; F-86-3-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 86-27)
  - Enterprise Development Centre, vol. 1, 1985 - 1990; F-86-3-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 86-27)
    Creator's original file classification code: B.2.5.
  - Enterprise Development Centre, vol. 2, 1985 - 1990; F-86-3-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 86-27)
  - Institute for Applied Logic, 1985 - 1992; F-86-3-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 86-27)
  - Institute for Human Performance, 1985 - 1994; F-86-3-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 86-27)
  - Incubation Centre (Technical Enterprise Centre), vol. 1, 1986 - 1988; F-86-3-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 86-27)
    Creator's original file classification code: C.6.3.
  - Incubation Centre (Technical Enterprise Centre), vol. 2, 1986 - 1988; F-86-3-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 86-27)
  - Wireless Communications Research Centre, vol. 1, 1987 - 1989; F-86-3-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 86-28)
  - Wireless Communications Research Centre, vol. 2, 1987 - 1989; F-86-3-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 86-28)
  - BCIT Development Assist Centre, 1987 - 1991; F-86-3-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 86-28)
  - Back Testing Unit Centre (M. Allen), vol. 1, 1988 - 1992; F-86-3-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 86-28)
  - Back Testing Unit Centre (M. Allen), vol. 2, 1988 - 1992; F-86-3-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 86-28)
  - Centre for Image Sound Research, vol. 1, 1988 - 1993; F-86-3-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 86-28)
  - Centre for Image Sound Research, vol. 2, 1988 - 1993; F-86-3-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 86-29)
  - CISR - Integrated Media Centre, 1988 - 1994; F-86-3-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 86-29)
  - Business Development Centre, 1991; F-86-3-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 86-29)
  - Advanced Systems Institute, 1991; F-86-3-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 86-29)
  - Center for Image and Sound Research, 1992 - 1994; F-86-3-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 86-29)
  - Networks of Centres of Excellence: Tech. Transfer, 1992 - 1995; F-86-3-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 86-29)
  - Sustainable Development Research Institute, 1992 - 1998; F-86-3-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 86-29)
  - Networks of Centres of Excellence: Letters of Intent, 1994; F-86-3-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 86-29)
  - C.D. Howe Institute, 1994; F-86-3-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 86-29)
  - Networks of Centres of Excellence: UTECH, 1994; F-86-3-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 86-29)
  - Networks of Centres of Excellence: general, vol. 1, 1994 - 1995; F-86-3-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 86-30)
  - Networks of Centres of Excellence: general, vol. 2, 1994 - 1995; F-86-3-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 86-30)
  - Networks of Centres of Excellence: TL correspondence, 1994 - 1995; F-86-3-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 86-30)
  - Networks of Centres of Excellence: TIC correspondence, 1994 - 1995; F-86-3-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 86-30)
  - Networks of Centres of Excellence: TICS Letters of Intent, vol. 1, 1994 - 1995; F-86-3-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 86-30)
  - Networks of Centres of Excellence: TICS Letters of Intent, vol. 2, 1994 - 1995; F-86-3-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 86-30)
  - Medical Devices Development Centre (MDDC), 1994 - 1996; F-86-3-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 86-30)
  - Advanced Materials Joint University Proposal, 1994 - 1996; F-86-3-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 86-31)
  - Networks of Centres of Excellence: TIC, vol. 1, 1995; F-86-3-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 86-31)
  - Networks of Centres of Excellence: TIC, vol. 2, 1995; F-86-3-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 86-31)
  - Canada ASEAN Centre, 1995; F-86-3-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 86-31)
  - Institute for Sensor and Control Tech Steering Committee, 1995 - 1996; F-86-3-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 86-31)
  - Networks of Centres of Excellence: general, 1995 - 1996; F-86-3-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 86-31)
  - Telelearning NCE, 1995 - 1996; F-86-3-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 86-31)
- Research projects/iniatives, 1981 - 1996; F-86-4; 27 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to research projects and initiatives including liaison with the Tri-University Meson Facility (TRIUMF) and other external organizations on research projects, securing funding and establishing Research Chairs, and adjudicating project proposals.
  Document types include correspondence and working papers, reports, budgets and contracts.
  TRIUMF
  - Accelerator proposal, vol. 1, 1981 - 1985; F-86-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 86-31)
    Creator's original file classification code: 2.1.3.
  - Accelerator proposal, vol. 2, 1981 - 1985; F-86-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 86-32)
  - Accelerator proposal, vol. 3, 1981 - 1985; F-86-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 86-32)
  - TRIUMF general correspondence, vol. 1, 1986 - 1992; F-86-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 86-32)
  - TRIUMF general correspondence, vol. 2, 1986 - 1992; F-86-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 86-32)
  - TRIUMF general correspondence, vol. 3, 1986 - 1992; F-86-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 86-33)
  - VRP: Research Chairs: Fisheries Management, 1990 - 1995; F-86-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 86-33)
  - VRP: Research Chair: Smith, Management of Tech: Innovation, 1992 - 1995; F-86-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 86-33)
  - Physics: Pacific Gemological Associates, 1995; F-86-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 86-33)
  - TRIUMF contribution agreement, 1995 - 1996; F-86-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 86-33)
  - Research on Immigration and Integration in the Metropolis, vol. 1, 1995 - 1996; F-86-4-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 86-33)
  - Research on Immigration and Integration in the Metropolis, vol. 2, 1995 - 1996; F-86-4-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 86-33)
  - Research Chair: Management of Tech Change, 1995 - 1996; F-86-4-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 86-33)
  - VRP: Research Chairs: Thewalt, 1995 - 1996; F-86-4-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 86-33)
  - Virtual U, 1996; F-86-4-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 86-33)
- Committees, 1977 - 2000; F-86-5; 1.16 m of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the participation of the Vice-President, Research on various SFU and non-SFU committees.
  For a complete list of committees see the sub-series descriptions.
  Document types include correspondence, working papers, agendas and minutes, reports and publications.
  - SFU Committees, 1977 - 2000; F-86-5-1; 75 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the participation of the Vice-President, Research on university committees.
    - Senate Library Committee, 1985 - 1990; F-86-5-1-1; 5 cm of textual records
      Senate Library Committee
      - Senate Library Committee, vol. 1, 1985 - 1990; F-86-5-1-1-1 (Archival box - standard 86-34)
      - Senate Library Committee, vol. 2, 1985 - 1990; F-86-5-1-1-2 (Archival box - standard 86-34)
      - Senate Library Committee, vol. 3, 1985 - 1990; F-86-5-1-1-3 (Archival box - standard 86-34)
    - University Research Council, 1992 - 1993; F-86-5-1-2; 2 cm of textual records
      - University Research Council, 1992 - 1993; F-86-5-1-2-1 (Archival box - standard 86-34)
    - IMC Futures Committee, 1985 - 1986; F-86-5-1-3; 2 cm of textual records
      IMC Futures Committee
      - IMC Futures Committee, 1985 - 1986; F-86-5-1-3-1 (Archival box - standard 86-34)
    - Presidential Committee on University Planning, 1996; F-86-5-1-4; 2 cm of textual records
      Presidential Committee on University Planning
      - Presidential Committee on University Planning, 1996; F-86-5-1-4-1 (Archival box - standard 86-34)
    - Havanna Steering Committee, 1994 - 1997; F-86-5-1-5; 2 cm of textual records
      - Havanna Steering Committee, 1994 - 1997; F-86-5-1-5-1 (Archival box - standard 86-34)
    - Animal Care Committee, 1987 - 1990; F-86-5-1-6; 2 cm of textual records
      - Animal Care Committee, 1987 - 1990; F-86-5-1-6-1 (Archival box - standard 86-34)
    - Diamond University Club Board, 1997 - 1999; F-86-5-1-7; 2 cm of textual records
      Diamond University Club. Board of Directors
      - Diamond University Club correspondence and minutes, 1997 - 1999; F-86-5-1-7-1 (Archival box - standard 86-35)
    - University Ethics Review Committee, 1980 - 2000; F-86-5-1-8; 24 cm of textual records
      - University Ethics Review Committee correspondence, 1980 - 1982; F-86-5-1-8-1 (Archival box - standard 86-35)
      - Ethics meetings and minutes, 1982 - 1990; F-86-5-1-8-2 (Archival box - standard 86-35)
      - Committee minutes, vol. 1, 1991 - 1996; F-86-5-1-8-3 (Archival box - standard 86-35)
      - Committee minutes, vol. 2, 1991 - 1996; F-86-5-1-8-4 (Archival box - standard 86-35)
      - Committee minutes, vol. 3, 1991 - 1996; F-86-5-1-8-5 (Archival box - standard 86-35)
      - Ethics external review, 1996 - 1998; F-86-5-1-8-6 (Archival box - standard 86-36)
      - Committee minutes, 1997; F-86-5-1-8-7 (Archival box - standard 86-36)
      - Committee minutes, vol. 1, 1998; F-86-5-1-8-8 (Archival box - standard 86-36)
      - Committee minutes, vol. 2, 1998; F-86-5-1-8-9 (Archival box - standard 86-36)
      - Committee minutes, vol. 3, 1998; F-86-5-1-8-10 (Archival box - standard 86-36)
      - Ethics Policy Revision Task Force, 1998 - 2000; F-86-5-1-8-11 (Archival box - standard 86-36)
      - Committee minutes, vol. 1, 1999; F-86-5-1-8-12 (Archival box - standard 86-36)
      - Committee minutes, vol. 2, 1999; F-86-5-1-8-13 (Archival box - standard 86-37)
    - University Publications Committee, 1979 - 1998; F-86-5-1-9; 18 cm of textual records
      - Correspondence and minutes, vol. 1, 1979 - 1985; F-86-5-1-9-1 (Archival box - standard 86-37)
      - Correspondence and minutes, vol. 2, 1979 - 1985; F-86-5-1-9-2 (Archival box - standard 86-37)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1980 - 1983; F-86-5-1-9-3 (Archival box - standard 86-37)
      - Economic inquiry, 1980 - 1985; F-86-5-1-9-4 (Archival box - standard 86-37)
      - Le Line/Coast Line, 1981 - 1983; F-86-5-1-9-5 (Archival box - standard 86-37)
      - Glossa Review, vol. 1, 1981 - 1984; F-86-5-1-9-6 (Archival box - standard 86-37)
      - Glossa Review, vol. 2, 1981 - 1984; F-86-5-1-9-7 (Archival box - standard 86-37)
      - Correspondence, 1982 - 1983; F-86-5-1-9-8 (Archival box - standard 86-37)
      - Journal of Macromarketing, 1982 - 1984; F-86-5-1-9-9 (Archival box - standard 86-37)
      - Westcoast Review, 1982 - 1984; F-86-5-1-9-10 (Archival box - standard 86-37)
      - History - Cleveland, W., 1982 - 1984; F-86-5-1-9-11 (Archival box - standard 86-37)
      - International History Review, 1983; F-86-5-1-9-12 (Archival box - standard 86-38)
      - Philosophy - Copp, D. and Zimmerman, S., 1983 - 1984; F-86-5-1-9-13 (Archival box - standard 86-38)
      - Archaeology - Skinner and Lazenby, 1983 - 1984; F-86-5-1-9-14 (Archival box - standard 86-38)
      - Library - Groves, P.E., 1984; F-86-5-1-9-15 (Archival box - standard 86-38)
      - Correspondence, 1993 - 1998; F-86-5-1-9-16 (Archival box - standard 86-38)
    - President's Research Grant Committee, 1977 - 1983; F-86-5-1-10; 13 cm of textual records
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, 1977 - 1980; F-86-5-1-10-1 (Archival box - standard 86-38)